{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771627486","data":{"timestamp":" 947771627486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771635493","data":{"timestamp":" 947771635493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771644120","data":{"timestamp":" 947771644119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771644353","data":{"timestamp":" 947771644353"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771645326","data":{"timestamp":" 947771645326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771646604","data":{"timestamp":" 947771646604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771649519","data":{"timestamp":" 947771649518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771650362","data":{"timestamp":" 947771650362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771650674","data":{"timestamp":" 947771650674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771651918","data":{"timestamp":" 947771651917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771655449","data":{"timestamp":" 947771655448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771656444","data":{"timestamp":" 947771656444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771656708","data":{"timestamp":" 947771656707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771657660","data":{"timestamp":" 947771657659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771660536","data":{"timestamp":" 947771660535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771661574","data":{"timestamp":" 947771661573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771662054","data":{"timestamp":" 947771662054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771666627","data":{"timestamp":" 947771666626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771666715","data":{"timestamp":" 947771666715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a71d9511-0c28-43a4-869e-8ca60a6ac86a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771681946","data":{"timestamp":" 947771681946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" c088ff8f-4ddf-4079-a3cd-dae787f3dd67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_gha-mwi-nda"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771717818","data":{"timestamp":" 947771717818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" c088ff8f-4ddf-4079-a3cd-dae787f3dd67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_yi-nda-swa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771734106","data":{"timestamp":" 947771734105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" c088ff8f-4ddf-4079-a3cd-dae787f3dd67"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_yi-nda-swa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771744015","data":{"timestamp":" 947771744015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 9b4d5a8b-9ae5-4e21-91e1-fae639f5ea5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771744908","data":{"timestamp":" 947771744908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 9b4d5a8b-9ae5-4e21-91e1-fae639f5ea5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771755390","data":{"timestamp":" 947771755390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771755776","data":{"timestamp":" 947771755775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771756019","data":{"timestamp":" 947771756019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771756343","data":{"timestamp":" 947771756342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771756589","data":{"timestamp":" 947771756588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771760084","data":{"timestamp":" 947771760084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771760384","data":{"timestamp":" 947771760384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771761293","data":{"timestamp":" 947771761293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771761725","data":{"timestamp":" 947771761725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771764722","data":{"timestamp":" 947771764722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771765010","data":{"timestamp":" 947771765010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771765867","data":{"timestamp":" 947771765866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771766545","data":{"timestamp":" 947771766545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771767290","data":{"timestamp":" 947771767289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771767625","data":{"timestamp":" 947771767625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771767906","data":{"timestamp":" 947771767905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771768226","data":{"timestamp":" 947771768225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771768493","data":{"timestamp":" 947771768493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771772238","data":{"timestamp":" 947771772237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771772635","data":{"timestamp":" 947771772634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771772781","data":{"timestamp":" 947771772780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771843918","data":{"timestamp":" 947771843918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" e4f3be35-9777-476c-99d9-818c39432257"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771854465","data":{"timestamp":" 947771854464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771854698","data":{"timestamp":" 947771854697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771855669","data":{"timestamp":" 947771855669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771856957","data":{"timestamp":" 947771856957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771859923","data":{"timestamp":" 947771859923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771860780","data":{"timestamp":" 947771860778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771861103","data":{"timestamp":" 947771861103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771862358","data":{"timestamp":" 947771862357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771865929","data":{"timestamp":" 947771865929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771866925","data":{"timestamp":" 947771866924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771867184","data":{"timestamp":" 947771867183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771868136","data":{"timestamp":" 947771868135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771871080","data":{"timestamp":" 947771871079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771872127","data":{"timestamp":" 947771872127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771872606","data":{"timestamp":" 947771872606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771874247","data":{"timestamp":" 947771874246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771874320","data":{"timestamp":" 947771874320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 7b44e297-de4e-49e0-88f0-c702751edf8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771885174","data":{"timestamp":" 947771885174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1ab37a32-b144-456b-9d16-255da740f87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nji-nda-pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nda"," userResponse":" nda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771888062","data":{"timestamp":" 947771888061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1ab37a32-b144-456b-9d16-255da740f87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nji-nda-pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771897865","data":{"timestamp":" 947771897865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1ab37a32-b144-456b-9d16-255da740f87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nji-nda-pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771907005","data":{"timestamp":" 947771907004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1ab37a32-b144-456b-9d16-255da740f87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nji-nda-pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771913983","data":{"timestamp":" 947771913983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1ab37a32-b144-456b-9d16-255da740f87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nji-nda-pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nda..nda.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771923732","data":{"timestamp":" 947771923732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1ab37a32-b144-456b-9d16-255da740f87d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nda..nda.syl.rand.all.stat.show.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nda_nji-nda-pe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771932560","data":{"timestamp":" 947771932560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771932783","data":{"timestamp":" 947771932783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771933747","data":{"timestamp":" 947771933747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771935020","data":{"timestamp":" 947771935020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771937894","data":{"timestamp":" 947771937894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771938737","data":{"timestamp":" 947771938737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771939050","data":{"timestamp":" 947771939050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771940283","data":{"timestamp":" 947771940283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771943767","data":{"timestamp":" 947771943767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771944749","data":{"timestamp":" 947771944749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771945003","data":{"timestamp":" 947771945003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771945946","data":{"timestamp":" 947771945946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771948774","data":{"timestamp":" 947771948774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771949807","data":{"timestamp":" 947771949807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771950280","data":{"timestamp":" 947771950280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771954782","data":{"timestamp":" 947771954782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771954843","data":{"timestamp":" 947771954843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771962828","data":{"timestamp":" 947771962828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947774990393","data":{"timestamp":" 947774990392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947774998144","data":{"timestamp":" 947774998144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.nda..ndu.asc.lc.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775008310","data":{"timestamp":" 947775008310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775017555","data":{"timestamp":" 947775017554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 6a2e7026-5734-4b51-9afd-da74bb8bebf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775431318","data":{"timestamp":" 947775431318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mko"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775439893","data":{"timestamp":" 947775439893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775447088","data":{"timestamp":" 947775447088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775456299","data":{"timestamp":" 947775456299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775463624","data":{"timestamp":" 947775463624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775474133","data":{"timestamp":" 947775474132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775489383","data":{"timestamp":" 947775489383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775496709","data":{"timestamp":" 947775496709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775505027","data":{"timestamp":" 947775505027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775510449","data":{"timestamp":" 947775510449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775519261","data":{"timestamp":" 947775519261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775522641","data":{"timestamp":" 947775522641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775528658","data":{"timestamp":" 947775528658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775534632","data":{"timestamp":" 947775534632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 1c72dc28-72d8-406c-9734-1abc740a7377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775544056","data":{"timestamp":" 947775544056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775544280","data":{"timestamp":" 947775544280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775545252","data":{"timestamp":" 947775545252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775546535","data":{"timestamp":" 947775546534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775549465","data":{"timestamp":" 947775549465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775550320","data":{"timestamp":" 947775550320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775550639","data":{"timestamp":" 947775550639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775551886","data":{"timestamp":" 947775551885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775555471","data":{"timestamp":" 947775555470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775556463","data":{"timestamp":" 947775556463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775556721","data":{"timestamp":" 947775556721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775557674","data":{"timestamp":" 947775557674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775560655","data":{"timestamp":" 947775560655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775561698","data":{"timestamp":" 947775561698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775562181","data":{"timestamp":" 947775562181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775566746","data":{"timestamp":" 947775566745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775566830","data":{"timestamp":" 947775566830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 5b5e551f-bbd3-4d6d-bf01-fd33bd72ef36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775578683","data":{"timestamp":" 947775578683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mwo-mme-vi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775583927","data":{"timestamp":" 947775583927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mme-bi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775588553","data":{"timestamp":" 947775588552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_fi-ta-mme"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775593280","data":{"timestamp":" 947775593280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ng'o-ve-mme"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775598023","data":{"timestamp":" 947775598023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-cha-mme"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775602777","data":{"timestamp":" 947775602777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-mme-no"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775607585","data":{"timestamp":" 947775607585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_ho-mme-mcho"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775613316","data":{"timestamp":" 947775613316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_mna-po-mme"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775618285","data":{"timestamp":" 947775618284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_sha-mme-ze"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775623137","data":{"timestamp":" 947775623136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mme"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775628923","data":{"timestamp":" 947775628922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775673504","data":{"timestamp":" 947775673503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" a15219eb-22a6-457d-b2b1-d22cf3c4b9f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mme..mme.syl.rand.all.stat.show.66"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mme_nji-mko-mme"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775684315","data":{"timestamp":" 947775684314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" MMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775687298","data":{"timestamp":" 947775687298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775688898","data":{"timestamp":" 947775688897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" MME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775692252","data":{"timestamp":" 947775692251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775693830","data":{"timestamp":" 947775693830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" MMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775696862","data":{"timestamp":" 947775696862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775698428","data":{"timestamp":" 947775698428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMO"," userResponse":" MMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775701692","data":{"timestamp":" 947775701691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775703241","data":{"timestamp":" 947775703241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" MMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775707009","data":{"timestamp":" 947775707009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775709025","data":{"timestamp":" 947775709025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775709183","data":{"timestamp":" 947775709183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 46e29abd-a824-4284-996b-dcbc3aff00e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mmu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775718684","data":{"timestamp":" 947775718683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775718911","data":{"timestamp":" 947775718911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775719891","data":{"timestamp":" 947775719891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775721176","data":{"timestamp":" 947775721176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775724121","data":{"timestamp":" 947775724120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775724970","data":{"timestamp":" 947775724969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775725287","data":{"timestamp":" 947775725287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775726528","data":{"timestamp":" 947775726528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775730115","data":{"timestamp":" 947775730115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775731115","data":{"timestamp":" 947775731114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775731375","data":{"timestamp":" 947775731374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775732329","data":{"timestamp":" 947775732329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775735267","data":{"timestamp":" 947775735267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775736310","data":{"timestamp":" 947775736309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775736786","data":{"timestamp":" 947775736786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775741368","data":{"timestamp":" 947775741366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775741480","data":{"timestamp":" 947775741480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.mma..mmu.asc.lc.44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775748972","data":{"timestamp":" 947775748971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" cc5a389e-bb33-4a7c-8be1-48053bb6d5c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775766911","data":{"timestamp":" 947775766911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775775799","data":{"timestamp":" 947775775798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775785650","data":{"timestamp":" 947775785650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775790882","data":{"timestamp":" 947775790882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775800439","data":{"timestamp":" 947775800439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775809355","data":{"timestamp":" 947775809355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775817382","data":{"timestamp":" 947775817382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775825220","data":{"timestamp":" 947775825220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775835103","data":{"timestamp":" 947775835103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775841592","data":{"timestamp":" 947775841592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775853935","data":{"timestamp":" 947775853935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775861556","data":{"timestamp":" 947775861555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775870192","data":{"timestamp":" 947775870191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 27536415-3005-4390-b69f-46be86b6f020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775888151","data":{"timestamp":" 947775888150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775897766","data":{"timestamp":" 947775897766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775906500","data":{"timestamp":" 947775906499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775915924","data":{"timestamp":" 947775915923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8+0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775926772","data":{"timestamp":" 947775926771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775937116","data":{"timestamp":" 947775937116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775945221","data":{"timestamp":" 947775945221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775952330","data":{"timestamp":" 947775952329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775959537","data":{"timestamp":" 947775959537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775966356","data":{"timestamp":" 947775966355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775974999","data":{"timestamp":" 947775974999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_165335"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}